Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Domestic Advertisements, part 1, 1875-2001 and undated, bulk 1920s-1990s RL.00687
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Small Files Series, 1901-1997 and undated
  - S Small Files, 1927-1990s
    - Sherwin-Williams Co., 1991, 1996-1997 (Box SS1)
      [See also Oversize Folder 53.]
    - ShowBiz Pizza (Chuck E. Cheese), 1993-1995 (Box SS1)
    - Showtime/The Movie Channel, 1983-1984, 1986 (Box SS1)
    - Signal Co., 1969, 1980-1982 (Box SS1)
    - Silk Greenhouse, ca. 1990s (Box SS1)
    - Simmons Company, 1927-1928, 1930, 1974-1977 (Box SS2)
    - Singer Co., 1964-1972 (Box SS2)
    - Six Flags Over Georgia, 1982-1989 (Box SS2)
    - Smith, Alexander: see Alexander Smith (Box SS2)
    - Société Générale, 1990-1992 (Box SS2)
    - Society Banking, 1993-1994 (Box SS2)
    - Sonat (Brouillard), 1982-1985 (Box SS2)
    - Southland Corporation, 1988-1996 (Box SS2)
      [See also Oversize Box OV26; Oversize Folders 54-55.]
    - Spring Air mattresses, 1983-1985 (Box SS3)
    - Squibb: see Bristol Myers Squibb (Box SS3)
    - Standard and Poor's, 1993-1995 (Box SS3)
    - Steinhauser Beer, 1984 (Box SS3)
    - Stick To Your Ribs, 1992 (Box SS3)
    - Stiller and Meara (JWT Entertainment Div.), 1976-1979 (Box SS3)
    - STP, 1976-1979 (Box SS3)
    - Stuart Anderson's Restaurants, 1989-1991 (Box SS3)
    - Successful Farming, 1970-1972 (Box SS3)
    - Sun Banks, Inc., 1982 (Box SS3)
      [See also Oversize Folder 57.]
    - Sunbeam, 1970-1977 (Box SS3)
    - Sun-Maid nectars, 1927 (Box SS3)
    - Sun Microsystems Inc., 1990, 1995-1996 (Box SS3)
    - Sunsweet Growers, 1995-1996 (Box SS3)
    - Survival Anglia Ltd. Wildlife Preservation, 1974, 1977-1979 (Box SS3)
    - Sylvania, 1955-1957 (Box SS3)
  - T Small Files, 1904-1991
    - Tappan, 1961, 1983 (Box TT1)
    - Target Group Index, 1974-1975 (Box TT1)
    - Teledyne Water Pik, 1981 (Box TT1)
    - Telos, 1984 (Box TT1)
    - Terson, 1981-1982 (Box TT1)
      [See also Oversize Folder 58.]
    - Texas American Banks (Brouillard), 1987-1988 (Box TT1)
      [See also Oversize Folder 59.]
    - Thomas B. Jeffery and Co. (Rambler automobile), 1904-1905 (Box TT1)
    - Thomas, Seth: see Seth Thomas (Box TT1)
    - Thorpe, 1974-1979 (Box TT1)
    - Timex, 1982-1983 (Box TT1)
      [See also Oversize Box OV27; Oversize Folder 53.]
    - Town House (Los Angeles), ca. 1930s (from microfilm) (Box TT1)
    - Toys 'R' Us, 1983 (Box TT1)
    - Tucker, Anthony and R.L. Day, 1987 (Box TT1)
    - Turkish Tourism, 1991 (Box TT1)
    - Tuskegee Institute, 1979-1981 (Box TT1)
  - U Small Files, ca. 1977-1997
    - Unionmutual (UNUM), 1986-1987 (Box UU1)
    - United Technologies, 1995-1997 (Box UU1)
    - Update on Health (JWT Entertainment Div.), ca. 1977 (Box UU1)
  - V Small Files, 1983-1984
    - Vacondo Real Estate, 1983 (Box VV1)
    - Vie de France, 1983-1984 (Box VV1)
  - W Small Files, 1927-1997
    - Wall Street Journal, 1942-1943, 1990-1991, 1996-1997 (Box WW1)
      [See also Dow Jones folder.]
    - Wanamaker, John: see John Wanamaker (Box WW1)
    - Ward Baking Co., 1941-1956 (Box WW1)
    - Washington Gas Light Co., 1969 (Box WW1)
    - Weather Channel, 1984-1985 (Box WW1)
    - Webb Young, trader (woolens), 1939-1950 (Box WW1)
    - Welch Grape Juice Company, 1927 (Box WW1)
    - Western Gear (Los Angeles), 1969 (Box WW1)
    - Western States Advertising Partnership, 1990 (Box WW1)
    - Westwood Lighting, 1983 (Box WW1)
    - W.H. Margerison and Co. (Martex), 1927 (Box WW1)
    - White Castle, 1993-1996 (Box WW1)
    - Whitehall Laboratories, 1967 (Box WW1)
    - William H. Rorer, Inc. Medical, 1974 (Box WW1)
    - Wilton Enterprise (Cake decorating and kitchen equipment), 1980-1985 (Box WW1)
    - Wine Advisory Board, ca. 1940s (Box WW1)
    - Wometco Home Theater (Landsdowne), 1979, 1982-1983 (Box WW1)
    - Wool Bureau, 1955-1956 (Box WW1)
    - W.R. Grace, 1975-1976 (Box WW1)
  - XYZ Small Files, ca. 1962 and undated
    - Yale Alumni, ca. 1962 (Box YY1)
    - Young's Apples: see Old Jim Young's Apples (Box YY1)
    - Yuban: see Arbuckle Brothers (Box YY1)
- Oversize Materials Series, 1916-1993 and undated
  - Oversize Boxes Subseries, 1916-1990 and undated
    - Alexander Smith, 1954 (Box OV1)
    - Allied Signal, 1989 (Box OV1)
    - AMAX, Inc., 1989 (Box OV1)
    - American Gas Association, 1984-1987 (Box OV1)
    - American Greetings, 1986-1987 (Box OV1)
    - American Hawaii Cruises, 1988-1990 (Box OV1)
    - American Library Association, 1989 (Box OV1)
    - American Petroleum Institute, 1964, 1967-1970, 5 folders (Box OV1)
      [See also Oversize Folder 3.]
    - American Petroleum Institute Auto Tours, 1970, 4 folders (Box OV2)
    - Ameritech, 1987 (Box OV2)
    - Andrew Jergens Co. (Woodbury Facial Soap), 1916 (Box OV2)
      Includes newspaper adsvertisement with slogan A Skin You Love to Touch.
    - Arbuckle Brothers (Yuban Coffee), 1916 (Box OV2)
    - Archdiocese of Detroit, 1976 (Box OV2)
    - Ballantine, P. and Sons, 1952-1954 (Box OV2)
    - Beatrice Foods (Arrowhead), 1986 (Box OV2)
    - Bell Atlantic, 1988 (Box OV2)
    - BellSouth Mobility, 1985, 1987 (Box OV2)
    - Bendix, 1982 (Box OV2)
    - Benetton, 1988 (Box OV2)
    - Blue Cross and Blue Shield, 1945-1966, 1985-1987 (Box OV2)
      [See also Oversize Folder 6; Oversize Folder 6.]
    - Bosch: see Robert Bosch Corp. (Box OV2)
    - Boys' Club of America, ca. 1970s (Box OV2)
    - Brand Names Foundation, 1964 (Box OV2)
    - Burger King, 1984 (Box OV2)
      [See also Oversize Folder 7.]
    - California State Summer School for the Arts, 1990 (Box OV2)
    - Campbell Taggart Associated Bakeries, 1967-1973 (Box OV2)
    - Carey-McFall Corp., 1984, 1989 (Box OV2)
    - Carhartt, 1990 (Box OV2)
      [See also Oversize Folder 9.]
    - Carte Blanche, 1966 (Box OV2)
    - Cellular One, 1988 (Box OV2)
    - Channel 7 Action News (Detroit), 1978-1980 (Box OV3)
      [See also WXYZ]
    - Chesebrough Ponds (including Cutex, Prince Matchabelli), 1930, 1934, 1947, 1953-1954, 1960, 1962, 1964-1965, 1967, 1969 (Box OV3)
      [See also Oversize Folder 11.]
    - Chevron, 1988, 1990 (Box OV3)
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad Co. (Milwaukee Road), 1963-1965, 1970 (Box OV3)
    - Chicago Tribune, 1970-1972 (Box OV3)
      [See also Oversize Folder 12.]
    - Christian Dior, 1981-1983 (Box OV3)
    - Cities Service Co., 1978 (Box OV3)
    - Computer Associates, 1988-1990 (Box OV3)
    - Congoleum Nairn, 1964-1975 (Box OV3)
    - Conroy's Flowers, 1988 (Box OV3)
    - Cystic Fibrosis Foundation (Ad Council), 1985 (Box OV3)
    - Daewoo, 1983-1987 (Box OV3)
    - Del Webb's Sun City (Los Angeles), ca. 1980s (Box OV3)
    - Dista Products (Deltakos), 1983 (Box OV3)
    - Domtar Gypsum, 1988 (Box OV3)
    - Dow Jones, 1990 (Box OV3)
    - Dunlop, 1983 (Box OV3)
    - Eastman Kodak--Consumer advertisements, 1930, 1943, 1957-1960, 1964-1965, 1967-1969, 1977, 1981-1982, 1984, 1986-1989, 6 folders (Box OV3)
      [See also Oversize Folder 15; Oversize Folder 15.]
    - Eastman Kodak--Trade and industrial advertisements, 1958-1960, 1964-1966, 1970-1971, 1983-1984, 1987, 3 folders (Box OV4)
    - Eaton Corporation, 1974-1981, 1986, 2 folders (Box OV4)
      [See also Oversize Folder 16; Oversize Folder 16.]
    - Eli Lilly, 1969, 1977-1979, 1980-1984, 1986, 2 folders (Box OV4)
    - Emery Worldwide, 1987-1988 (Box OV4)
    - Employees Mutuals of Wausau, 1959-1964 (Box OV4)
    - European-American Bank, 1975-1977 (Box OV4)
    - Federal Home Loan Mortgage Co., 1983-1984 (Box OV4)
    - Financial Security Assistance Inc., 1985 (Box OV4)
    - Firestone Tire and Rubber Co., 1969-1971 (Box OV4)
    - First National City Bank, 1967-1970 (Box OV4)
    - Flexco, 1986 (Box OV4)
    - Ford (Box OV5)
      [See also Oversize Folders 17-19.]
      - 1949-1953, General, 6 folders (Box OV5)
      - 1949-1950, Norman Strouse, 2 folders (Box OV5)
      - 1953, Trucks (Box OV5)
      - 1953, Dealers, 2 folders (Box OV6)
      - 1953, Dealers--Trucks (Box OV6)
      - 1954, General (Box OV6)
      - 1954-1955, Dealers, 4 folders (Box OV7)
      - 1956, Dealers, 5 folders (Box OV8)
      - 1956-1957, General, 2 folders (Box OV9)
      - 1957, Dealers, 2 folders (Box OV9)
      - 1957-1958, Trucks, 2 folders (Box OV9)
      - 1958, 1962-1963, 1966-1967, 1970, 1976, 1978, American Trucking Association (ATA-Ford was a member) (Box OV9)
      - 1958-1962, Cars, 5 folders (Box OV10)
      - 1959-1962, Trucks, 4 folders (Box OV10)
      - 1960, Dealers, 3 folders (Box OV10)
      - 1963-1964, Dealers, 3 folders (Box OV11)
      - 1963-1964, Trucks, 2 folders (Box OV11)
      - 1963-1965, Cars, 3 folders (Box OV11)
      - 1965-1967, Dealers, 3 folders (Box OV12)
      - 1965-1967, Trucks, 3 folders (Box OV12)
      - 1966-1967, Cars, 2 folders (Box OV12)
      - 1968-1970, Dealers, 3 folders (Box OV13)
      - 1968-1974, Cars, 7 folders (Box OV13)
      - 1968-1974, Trucks, 7 folders (Box OV13)
      - 1975, General (Box OV14)
      - 1975-1981, Cars, 7 folders (Box OV14)
      - 1975-1981, Dealers, 7 folders (Box OV14)
      - 1975-1981, Trucks, 7 folders (Box OV14)
      - 1982-1984, Dealers, 3 folders (Box OV15)
      - 1982-1985, Cars, 4 folders (Box OV15)
      - 1982-1985, Trucks, 4 folders (Box OV15)
      - 1983, General (Box OV15)
      - 1984, Racing (Box OV15)
      - 1985, Van (Aerostar) (Box OV15)
      - 1986-1989, 1991, Cars, 5 folders (Box OV16)
      - 1986-1989, 1991, Trucks, 5 folders (Box OV16)
      - 1988-1989, Dealers, 2 folders (Box OV16)
        Includes Army and Air Force Exchange Services-AAFES.
    - Frankfort Distillers Co., 1968-1969 (Box OV17)
    - Franklin State Bank, 1973-1974 (Box OV17)
    - French: see R.T. French (Box OV17)
    - G.D. Searle: see Searle Laboratories (Box OV17)
    - General Cigar Co. (White Owl), 1939 (Box OV17)
    - General Wine and Spirits (Ronrico), 1969-1970 (Box OV17)
    - Georgia Federal, 1988-1989 (Box OV17)
    - Gerber Products Co., 1983-1987 (Box OV17)
    - Gift America, 1973-1974 (Box OV17)
    - Goldman-Sachs, 1977-1989, 2 folders (Box OV17)
    - Goodyear, 1979-1981, 1983-1987, 4 folders (Box OV17)
    - Grand Union, 1982 (Box OV17)
    - Guerlain, 1986 (Box OV17)
    - Harris Corp., 1982 (Box OV18)
    - Health Alliance Plan, 1987 (Box OV18)
    - Health and Tennis Corp. of America, 1981-1987 (Box OV18)
      [See also Bally Manufacturing; Oversize Folder 21A.]
    - Hearst Corp., 1984 (Box OV18)
    - Henry Street Settlement, 1969 (Box OV18)
    - Hewlett Packard, 1980s (Box OV18)
    - Holiday Inns, Inc., 1972-1975 (Box OV18)
    - Hollywood Park, 1988 (Box OV18)
    - Hyatt Hotels, 1983-1987 (Box OV18)
    - IBM, 1986-1987 (Box OV18)
    - Institute for Health Maintenance, 1983 (Box OV18)
    - Institute of Life Insurance, 1957-1960, 1962-1965, 1968-1969, 1974 and undated (Box OV18)
    - International Spike, 1979 (Box OV18)
    - Irving Trust, 1921, 1924-1927, 1929, 1931-1932, 1937-1938, 1943, 1945-1947, 1952, 1959, 1960-1961, 1963-1969, 1972, 1975, 1979-1980, 1988 and undated, 4 folders (Box OV18)
      [See also Oversize Folder 22.]
    - Jantzen, Inc., 1970s (Box OV19)
    - Jenny Craig, 1989-1990 (Box OV19)
    - Johnson: see S.C. Johnson and Son (Box OV19)
    - Johnson and Johnson, 1969, 1975 (Box OV19)
    - Jos. Schlitz Brewing Co., 1981-1982 (Box OV19)
    - Julius Kayser and Co., 1916 (Box OV19)
    - J. Walter Thompson Co. (house ads), 1963-1964, 1989, 1991 (Box OV19)
      [See also Oversize Folder 24-26.]
    - J. Walter Thompson Entertainment Group, 1978-1980, 2 folders (Box OV19)
    - Kaiser Permanente, 1987-1988 (Box OV19)
    - Kawasaki Motors Corp., 1978-1982 (Box OV19)
    - Kellogg's, Inc., 1950s, 1987 (Box OV19)
    - Kemper, 1987 (Box OV19)
    - Kilpatrick's Bakeries, Inc., 1969 (Box OV19)
    - Kingsberry Homes Corp., 1959-1960, 1962 (Box OV19)
    - KNBC, 1968-1969 (Box OV19)
    - Kraft, 1933, 1946-1948, 1950-1957, 1969, 1974, 1983-1987, 6 folders (Box OV19)
      [See also Oversize Folders 26-28.]
    - Labbatt's, 1978, 1970s (Box OV19)
    - Lever Brothers, 1916-1918, 1925-1931, 7 folders (Box OV20)
      [See also Oversize Folder 29.]
    - Lever Brothers, 1932-1939, 1957-1958, 1960-1961, 1964-1966, 1969, 1987, 1989, 6 folders (Box OV21)
    - Liebmann Breweries (Rheingold), 1962-1963 (Box OV22)
    - Life Insurance Company of Virginia (LGFE), ca. 1982 (Box OV22)
    - Liggett and Myers, 1962, 1964-1969 and undated, 2 folders (Box OV22)
    - Lorillard, P., 1941 (Box OV22)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1988 (Box OV22)
    - Los Angeles Times, 1986 (Box OV22)
    - Manufacturer's Bank, 1974-1975 (Box OV22)
    - Marsh and McLennan, 1960-1970, 1972 (Box OV22)
    - Mass. Mutual Life Insurance Co., 1957-1962, 1964-1967 (Box OV22)
    - Matilda Bay Wines, 1987 (Box OV22)
    - McCulloch, 1987-1990 (Box OV22)
    - McDonnell Douglas, 1952, 1957, 1961, 1963, 1965, 1986-1987, 3 folders (Box OV23)
      [See also Oversize Folder 33.]
    - McGraw-Edison, 1955-1965 (Box OV23)
    - Mead Johnson and Co. (Metrecal), ca. 1960-1961 (Box OV23)
    - Medalist, 1987 (Box OV23)
    - Mellon Bank, 1982-1986 and undated (Box OV23)
    - Mennen, 1967, 1969 (Box OV23)
    - Mentholatum Co., 1963-1966 (Box OV23)
    - Miles Laboratories, 1968-1970, 1974-1975, 1978 (Box OV23)
    - Miller, 1985-1986 (Box OV23)
    - Mink International, 1970, 1973-1974, 1976-1980, 1986-1987 (Box OV23)
    - Municipal Bond Investors Assurance Corp. (MBIA), 1989-1990 (Box OV23)
    - Nestlé, 1982, 1987-1988 (Box OV23)
    - New Holland: see Sperry-New Holland (Box OV23)
    - New York World's Fair, 1962, 1964 (Box OV24)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1982-1987 (Box OV24)
      [See also Oversize Folder 37.]
    - Northam Warren (Cutex), 1917 (Box OV24)
    - Northeast Airlines, 1958-1960 (Box OV24)
    - Northern Telecom, 1981-1989, 2 folders (Box OV24)
      [See also Oversize Folder 38.]
    - Northern Trust Bank, 1986-1987 (Box OV24)
    - Northwestern Mutual Life Insurance Co., 1988-1990 (Box OV24)
    - Olivetti, 1980, 1982 (Box OV24)
    - Olympia, 1983 (Box OV24)
    - Original Appalachian Artworks, 1985 (Box OV24)
    - Orkin, 1988 (Box OV24A)
    - Oscar Mayer, 1977, 1987 (Box OV24A)
    - O'Sullivan Rubber Co., 1916 (Box OV24A)
    - Owens-Illinois, 1958-1960 (Box OV24A)
    - Parker Pen, 1947, 1949-1952, 1970, 1972-1973, 1980, 2 folders (Box OV24A)
    - P. Ballantine: see Ballantine (Box OV24A)
    - Phillips Petroleum, 1962-1966, 1968 and undated, 2 folders (Box OV24A)
    - Phone Mate, 1980s (Box OV25)
    - Platinum, 1977 (Box OV25)
    - Playcable, 1982 (Box OV25)
    - P. Lorillard: see Lorillard (Box OV25)
    - Prodigy, 1989 (Box OV25)
    - Publicker Distillers Products, Inc. (Inver House), 1974-1975 (Box OV25)
    - RCA, 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box OV25)
    - Reader's Digest, 1967-1969, 1973 (Box OV25)
    - Reynolds Aluminum, 1978-1979, 1980, 1982, 1984 (Box OV25)
    - R.J. Reynolds (Chung King), 1968 (Box OV25)
    - Robert Bosch Corp., 1988-1989 (Box OV25)
    - Rolex, 1966-1967, 1970, 1983 (Box OV25)
    - Roxane Laboratories, 1988 (Box OV25)
    - R.T. French, 1932, 1935, 1937, 1975, 1983-1984, 1986 (Box OV25)
    - Ryder, 1983 (Box OV25)
    - Saga Mink, 1970-1971, 1973, 1975 (Box OV25)
    - Salvatore Ferragamo, 1983 (Box OV25)
    - Samsonite (Toys), 1972 (Box OV25)
    - S.C. Johnson and Son, 1986 (Box OV25)
    - Scott Paper Co., 1936, 1958, 1960, 1963, 1964, 1968 (Box OV25)
      [See also Oversize Folder 41.]
    - Screenvision, 1978 (Box OV25)
    - Seagram Distillers Co., 1968-1969 (Box OV25)
    - Searle, Laboratories, 1977-1978, 1981 and undated (Box OV25)
    - Sears (consumer, Craftsman), 1969, 1979-1981, 2 folders (Box OV25)
      [See also Oversize Folders 42-46.]
    - Sears (Financial Network and Mortgage Corp.), 1987 (Box OV25)
    - Selchow and Righter, 1979 (Box OV25)
    - Seven-Up, 1947, 1950, 1952-1955, 1960-1961, 1964, 3 folders (Box OV25)
      [See also Oversize Folders 47-52.]
    - Shaw-Walker, 1978 (Box OV25)
    - Shell, 1937 (Box OV25)
    - Showtime, 1986 (Box OV25)
    - Signal Oil and Gas Co. (Garrett Corp.), 1967, 1969, 1979, 1981-1984 (Box OV25)
    - Simmons Co., 1928-ca. 1930 (Box OV25)
    - Simmons Market Research Bureau (SMRB), 1980 (Box OV25)
    - Singer, 1964-1968, 1971, 2 folders (Box OV26)
    - Six Flags, 1987-1989 (Box OV26)
    - Sonat, 1982 (Box OV26)
    - Southland (7-Eleven), 1989-1990 (Box OV26)
      [See also Oversize Folders 54-55.]
    - Sperry-New Holland, 1949, 1952-1959, 1963-1967, 1978-1979 (Box OV26)
    - Standard Brands (Chase and Sandborn), 1967 (Box OV26)
      [See also Oversize Folder 57; Oversize Folder 57.]
    - Standard Federal, 1987 (Box OV26)
    - STP, 1976-1977 (Box OV26)
    - Stuart Anderson, 1989 (Box OV26)
    - Sun Microsystems, 1990 (Box OV26)
    - Sylvania Products Inc., 1955-1957 (Box OV26)
    - Syntex Labs, 1980s (Box OV26)
    - Teledyne Water Pik, 1970s (Box OV26)
    - Tenneco Automotive, 1987, 1989 (Box OV26)
    - Texas-America Bancshares, 1987-1988 (Box OV26)
    - Textron, 1986 (Box OV26)
    - Timex, 1982-1984 (Box OV27)
    - Toys 'R' Us, 1987 (Box OV27)
    - Uncle Ben's Inc., 1983, 2 folders (Box OV27)
    - United States Marine Corps, early 1970s-1976, 1980-ca. 1990, 2 folders (Box OV27)
      [See also Oversize Folders 61-62.]
    - United Way, 1982, 1980s (Box OV28)
    - US Air, 1980s (Box OV28)
    - U.S. Sprint, 1987-1990 (Box OV28)
    - U.S. Treasury Savings Bonds (Ad Council), 1965 (Box OV28)
    - Vons, 1987 (Box OV28)
    - Warner-Lambert, 1963, 1965, 1967-1969, 1971, 1977-1982, 1986 (Box OV28)
    - Washington Gas Light Co., 1969 (Box OV28)
    - W.A. Taylor, 1980, 1983 (Box OV28)
    - W.F. Young, 1939, 1949, 1969, 1970, 1973 (Box OV28)
    - Wool Bureau, 1956-1957, 1959-1960 (Box OV28)
    - W.R. Grace, 1975-1976 (Box OV28)
  - Oversize Folders Subseries, 1921-1993 and undated
    - Advertising Council, 1948-1949, 1951 and undated (Folder 1)
      - American Economic System (Box OV28)
      - Nursing (Box OV28)
      - Religion in American Life (Box OV28)
      - United Nations (Box OV28)
      - U.S. Savings Bonds (Box OV28)
      - U.S. Security Bonds (Box OV28)
    - American Film Theatre, early 1970s (Box OV28, Folder 2)
    - American Petroleum Institute, 1969 (Box OV28, Folder 3)
    - American Red Cross, 1978-1981 and undated (Box OV28, Folder 4)
    - Bausch and Lomb, 1980 (Box OV28, Folder 5)
    - BellSouth, 1984 (Box OV28, Folder 6)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield, ca. 1970s-1980s (Box OV28)
    - Boy Scouts of Greater New York (Landsdowne), 1984 (Box OV28)
    - Burger King, ca. 1976-1980, 1987 (Box OV28, Folder 7)
    - Capitol, 1974 (Box OV28, Folder 8)
    - Carhartt, 1987 (Box OV28, Folder 9)
    - Champion, 1965, 1974, 1984, 1986 (Box OV28, Folder 10)
    - Chesebrough-Ponds, 1935-1936, 1954, 1960-1962 (Box OV28, Folder 11)
    - Chicago Tribune, 1970-1973 (Box OV28, Folder 12)
    - Christian Dior (Landsdowne), ca. 1982 (Box OV28, Folder 13)
    - Detroit Renaissance Events, Inc., 1984 (Box OV28)
    - Discover Card, 1985-1987 (Box OV28, Folder 14)
    - Eastman Kodak Co., 1930, 1938, ca. 1957-1959, 1965, 1968-1973, 1978, 1982-1984, 1987 (Box OV28, Folder 15)
    - Eaton Corp, 1974-1976 (Box OV28, Folder 16)
    - Ford Motor Company (Folder 17)
      - 1949-1957 (Box OV28)
      - 1949-1988 (Box OV28, Folder 18)
      - 1963-1987 (Box OV28, Folder 19)
    - Gerber baby food, 1989 (Box OV28, Folder 20)
    - Gillette, 1973-1977 (Box OV28)
    - Goldman Sachs, 1975-1976, 1978, 1980-1982 (Box OV28, Folder 21)
    - Hawaii Express, 1983 (Box OV28)
    - Health and Tennis Corp. of America, 1983 (Box OV28)
      [See also Bally Manufacturing Corp.]
    - Irving Trust, 1921, 1923, 1925, 1927-1928, 1979 (Box OV28, Folder 22)
    - Jovan, 1975, 1980-1981 (Box OV28, Folder 23)
    - J. Walter Thompson Co. (house advertisements, including LGFE) (Folder 24)
      - 1919-1984 (Box OV28)
      - 1964, 1980, 1984-1988 (Box OV28, Folder 25)
    - Kraft
      - Mayonnaise, 1930s (Box OV28, Folder 26)
      - Philadelphia Cream Cheese, 1951 (Box OV28, Folder 27)
      - Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box OV28, Folder 28)
    - Lever Brothers, 1957, 1964-1965, 1968-1969, 1981-1983, 1987 (Box OV28, Folder 29)
    - Liggett and Myers, 1963, 1965 and undated (Box OV28)
    - Löwenbräu, 1992-1994 (Box OV28, Folder 30)
    - Marathon Le Tourneau, 1983-1985 (Box OV28, Folder 31)
    - Marsh and McLennan, 1977-1981 (Box OV28)
    - Matilda Bay Wines, 1987 (Box OV28, Folder 32)
    - McDonnell Douglas, 1955, 1957, 1988-1994 (Box OV28, Folder 33)
    - Michigan National Corporation Banks, 1983 (Box OV28, Folder 34)
    - Miller, 1985 (Box OV28)
    - Monroe, 1974-1976, 1978-1979 and undated (Box OV28)
    - Motorola, 1994 (Box OV28)
    - Municipal Bond Investors Assurance Corp. (MBIA), 1986-1987 (Box OV28, Folder 35)
    - Munsingwear, Inc., 1982 (Box OV28)
    - NATO, 1957 (Box OV28, Folder 36)
    - New York Central Railroad, 1956 (Box OV28)
    - New York Chamber of Commerce, 1979 (Box OV28)
    - New York Dress Institute, 1943 (Box OV28)
    - New York Shipping Association, Inc., 1963 (Box OV28)
    - New York World's Fair, 1962-1964 (Box OV28)
    - Nixon-Lodge campaign, 1960 (Box OV28)
    - Norfolk Southern, 1986 (Box OV28, Folder 37)
    - Northern Telecom, 1986-1993 (Box OV28, Folder 38)
    - Orkin, 1987 (Box OV28, Folder 37)
    - Pan American World Airways, 1942, 1953-1958, 1983 (Box OV28, Folder 39)
    - Phillips Petroleum, ca. 1961 (Box OV28, Folder 40)
    - Purolator Products, Inc., ca. 1960s (Box OV28)
    - Ryder, 1984 (Box OV28)
    - Scott Paper Co., 1961-1962, 1964 and undated (Box OV28, Folder 41)
    - Sears (Folder 42)
      - Corporate, 1968-1978 (Box OV28)
      - Craftsman, 1982 (Box OV28, Folder 43)
      - Die-Hard, 1967-1968 (Box OV28, Folder 44)
      - Tires, 1967, 2 folders (Box OV28, Folder 45-46)
    - Seven-Up (Folder 47)
      - 1947-1957 (Box OV28)
      - 1955-1971 (Box OV28, Folder 48)
      - 1958-1978 (Box OV28, Folder 49)
      - 1959-1960 (Box OV28, Folder 50)
      - 1965, 1975 (Box OV28, Folder 51)
      - 1968, 1970s (Box OV28, Folder 52)
    - Sherwin Williams, 1992 (Box OV28, Folder 53)
    - Sinclair (Timex), 1983 (Box OV28)
    - Southland
      - 1981 (Box OV28)
      - 1989-1993 (Box OV28, Folder 55)
    - Squibb, 1951-1952, 1955 and undated (Box OV28, Folder 56)
    - Standard Brands, 1959-1960, 1968 (Box OV28, Folder 57)
    - Sun Banks, 1983-1984 (Box OV28)
    - Tenneco Automotive, 1982-1983 (Box OV28)
    - Terson, 1982 (Box OV28, Folder 58)
    - Texas American Bancshares (Fort Worth Bank), 1987 (Box OV28, Folder 59)
    - Textron
      - 1969-1970 (Box OV28)
      - 1971-1984 (Box OV28, Folder 60)
    - U.S. Marine Corps, ca. 1964, 1974-1975 and undated, 2 folders (Box OV28, Folder 61-62)
- Product Classification Index
  - Arts and entertainment
    - American Film Theatre (Oversize only)
    - Brookfield Zoo (Small Files Series)
    - California Arts Council (Main Files Series)
    - California State Summer School for the Arts (Oversize only)
    - Detroit Institute of Arts (Small Files Series)
    - Detroit Renaissance Events (Detroit Grand Prix III) (Small Files Series)
    - Eastman Kodak (Main Files Series)
    - Fine Arts Museum of San Francisco (Small Files Series)
    - Hollywood Park Race Track (Small Files Series)
    - King's Island (Small Files Series)
    - Los Angeles County Museum of Art (Small Files Series)
    - Museum of Contemporary Art (Main Files Series)
    - New York City Opera (Small Files Series)
    - New York Jazz Museum (Small Files Series)
    - New York World Fair Corp. (Small Files Series)
    - PGA 61st Golf Championship (Small Files Series)
    - Radio City Music Hall, Snow White (Small Files Series)
    - Really Rosie (Small Files Series)
    - Six Flags Over Georgia (Small Files Series)
  - Business